

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Summary_

Current member and back-end developer at Better Games LLC. 6+ years experience specializing in security, data mining and recognition, and backend development for both web and native applications. Interested in problem solving, designing and implementing applications, and cyber security.

Work Experience

Michigan State University School of Planning, Design and Construction

East Lansing

Developer February 2019 - Present

Utilize ArcGIS for displaying housing data statistics on a PHP website.

Better Games LLC

FOUNDER November 2018 - Present

- Designed and implemented the C# backend as well as the netcode used to communicate with Steam
- · Handled communication with publishers as well as documentation for forming the company

Michigan State University Institute for Cyber-Enabled Research

East Lansing

Technical Assistant July 2017 - February 2019

- Wrote build scripts and maintained packages for the HPCC.
- Worked on upgrading systems to a new node cluster.

Michigan State University RS&GIS

East Lansing

Web Developer November 2015 - March 2017

Wrote the admissions portal and course registration for the college of Social Work as well as course registration for the school of Human Resources and Labor Relations.

Michigan State University Plant Research Laboratory

East Lansing

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

December 2012 - January 2015

Worked on several papers and projects with faculty including: Visual Phenomics, image recognition and processing for calculating photosynthetic data of plants and PhenoMath, analyze the output from Visual Phenomics, running pattern recognition and outlier detection algorithms to determine interesting data-points.

Public Projects _____

Puttin' Around

Online multiplayer mini golf game written in C-sharp running off of the unity engine. Distributed via Steam, and run off of dedicated servers

2019

MSU Social Work Undergraduate Application system

EASY APPLICATION FOR MSU STUDENTS TO APPLY TO THE SCHOOL OF SOCIAL WORK. ADMINISTRATION PORTAL NOT PUBLICLY AVALIABLE. WRITTEN IN PHP WITH A MYSOL DATABASE.

2017

MSU School of Human Resources and Labor Relations Course Registration

EASY WEB REGISTRATION FOR THE MSU SCHOOL OF HRLR, WRITTEN IN PHP WITH A MYSQL BACKEND.

2017

EAT

A NODE.JS WEBSITE TO PARSE AND COMBINE DINING MENUS FOR VARIOUS SOURCES.

2017

Education

Michigan State University

East Lansing

2011 - 2018

COMPUTER SCIENCE

• Placed 4th at the ACM ICPC 2012.

• Placed 3rd at MHacks 1.

Skills_

Languages C, C++, C#, Coq, Go, Java, Javascript, PHP, Python, Rust, SQL

Interests Cyber Security, Penetration Testing, Machine Learning, Pattern Recognition